조이? 안에 있어?
Joey? Are you in there?
- 레이첼이야
- 조이, 레이첼과 얘기해
-That's Rachel.
-You have to talk to her.
안 돼, 그날 밤 이후로
너무 어색하단 말야
I can't. Not after the other night.
It's too weird.
나 여기 없다고 해
Don't tell her I'm here.
이거 먹지 마!
Don't eat that!
- 안녕!
- 레이첼
-Hey!
-Hey, Rachel.
조이 여깄어?
Is Joey here?
- 난 못 봤는데, 당신은?
- 못 봤어
-I don't see him. You?
-No.
설탕 그릇 안에 있는지도 몰라
조이? 없네
Maybe he's in the sugar bowl.
Joey? Nope.
둘이 서로 재밌다면야
Well, at least you make
each other laugh.
- 왜 그래?
- 조이가 통 안 보여, 그날
-What's up?
-I haven't seen him since he said..
그러니까...
how he, you know..
몰라, 날 피하는 것 같아
I don't know,
I think he's avoiding me.
바닥에 웬 베이글이야?
Why is that bagel on the floor?
- 게임하고 있었어
- 챈들러 벗겨놓고?
-We were playing a game.
-Was Chandler naked?
고리 던지기랑 비슷해?
Sort of like a ring-toss
kind of situation?
- 맞아!
- 뭐? 아냐! 아냐!
-Sure!
-What? No! No!
좋아, 조이 만나면 좀 전해줄래?
All right, listen. If you see Joey,
will you just tell him that..?
내가 보고 싶다고 말야
Tell him I miss him.
- 자, 들었어?
- 그래, 베이글 던지기?
-Okay. Did you hear that?
-Yeah. That naked bagel game?
베이글 구멍이 꽤 작은데
Dude, I don't know. That's a pretty
small hole.
- 레이첼과 얘기해
- 난 못해
-You've gotta talk to her.
-I can't.
거절당한다는 게 어떤 건지
너희는 모를 거야
You guys don't know what it's like
to get shot down.
내가 모른다고?
I don't know what that's like?
25살 때까지 '사랑한다'고 하면
'유치해'만 듣던 나야
Until I was 25, I thought the response
to "I love you" was "Oh, crap."
내가 거절을 모른다고?
No rejection?
뚱보 캠프에서 왕따당했던 나야
I got shot down at fat camp.
애들은 배고프면 정말 치사해져
Boy, kids are mean
when they're hungry.
그래서 어떻게 하라고?
So, what do I do?
레이첼과 다시 얘기 안 할 거야?
It's Rachel.
You're gonna never talk to her again?
이상하고 어색하겠지
하지만 시도는 해봐야잖아
It's weird and it's awkward,
but you gotta at least try.
그래, 알았어
Yeah, okay.
거기 걸려있었단 걸...
I forgot this was on your..
게임 안 했어!
We didn't play it!
프렌즈 시즌 8
'피비의 찻잎점'
'센트럴 퍼크'
바닥에 찻잎이 남는
모양을 보고 점 쳐줄게
I'll look at your tea leaves
and tell your fortune.
- 찻잎점도 쳐?
- 오랫동안 해왔는 걸
-You read tea leaves?
-I've done it for years.
너무 정확해서 그만 뒀지만 말야
I actually stopped
because I was so accurate.
솔직히 삶이 재미있는 이유가
And one of the great joys
of life..
한치 앞을 못 보기 때문이잖아
is its wondrous unpredictability,
you know?
게다가 차 마시면 설사도 나고
And also,
tea tends to give me the trots.
- 자, 다 마셨어, 점 쳐봐
- 좋아
-Okay. I'm done. Read mine.
-Okay.
사다리네
I see a ladder.
승진을 하거나 아니면
비명횡사한다는 뜻이야
Which can mean either a promotion
or a violent death.
난 수석 요리사야
더 이상 승진할 데가 없어
I'm the head chef.
I can't get promoted.
다음?
Who's next?
다 마셨어, 점 쳐줘
I'm done. Do mine.
좋아
Okay.
동그라미네
Oh! Okay, I see a circle.
이건 아기를 낳게 되거나 아니면
Which can either mean
you're having a baby..
과학적인 발견을
하게 된다는 뜻이야!
or you'll make
a scientific discovery!
내가 요즘 검사실에서
엄청 시간을 보내고 있지
Well, I have been spending
a lot of time in the lab.
- 네 점도 쳐봐
- 알았어
-What does yours say, Pheebs?
-All right.
만세!
Wow! Yay!
남자를 만나게 된데!
아주 빠른 시일 내에 말야!
Oh, I'm gonna meet a guy!
And really soon!
내 꿈속의 남자라는데
He's gonna be the man of my dreams.
어젯밤 꿈속의 남자는 아닐 거야
Probably not the guy
I had a dream about last night.
내 셔츠 본 사람 없어?
Has anyone seen my shirt?
연한 연어색 와이셔츠 말야
It's a button-down, like
a faded salmon color?
분홍색 와이셔츠 말야?
You mean your pink shirt?
연한 연어색 셔츠야
Faded salmon color?
분홍색 와이셔츠 못 봤어
No, I haven't seen your pink shirt.
모나 집에 두고 왔나 봐
이럴 줄 알았다니까!
I must have left it at Mona's.
I knew it!
여성복 코너에 가서 사면되잖아
I'm sure you can get another one
at Ann Taylor's.
내가 즐겨 입는 거란 말야
아주 좋아한다고
That's my favorite shirt.
I love it.
모나한테 돌려달라고 해
Ask Mona to give it back.
모르겠어, 그래야겠지
I don't know. I could.
그런데 끝이 안좋게 끝났거든
We didn't really end things
on good terms.
다시 만나면 모나가 했던
마지막 말을 무시하게 돼
If I went, I'd be ignoring the
one thing she asked me to do..
"똥구멍에 얼굴 쳐박고 죽어"
jump up my own ass and die.
얘들아
Oh, wait a second, you guys?
요즘 나 저 남자랑 계속 부딪쳐
I've been seeing that guy
everywhere I go.
버스에서도 만나고
서점에서도 만났다니까
We take the same bus,
go to the same bookstore.
꿈속의 남자인지도 몰라
Maybe he's the tea guy.
방금 봤어?
Did you see that?
널 쫙 훑어봤잖아! 너무 귀여워!
He totally checked you out!
And he is so cute!
내 건 '빌리지 피플'이네
무슨 뜻이야?
Mine is a picture of the Village
People. What does that mean?
안녕
Hi.
Hey.
- 안녕
-Hi.
피비는 차 마시면 설사한대!
Tea gives Phoebe the trots!
조이랑 괜찮을 줄 알았단 말야
I thought Joey and l
would be okay..
그런데 너무 어색해서 미치겠어
but we don't know
how to be together.
그리고 전부터 말하려고 했는데
By the way,
I've been meaning to say this.
미리 알고 있었으면
귀띔이라도 해줬어야지
If you guys knew about this,
a heads-up would have been nice.
살짝 말야
Just a little, you know.
"조이가 널 사랑한대, 준비해둬"
"Joey loves you.
Be prepared."
- 미안해
- 다음부턴 잘해
-Sorry.
-Well, for next time.
- 시간이 해결해줄 거야
- 어떻게 알아?
-It's tough, but things will improve.
-How do you know?
만약 상황이 악화돼서
What if it gets worse and worse..
같은 방에 있지도 못하면 어떡해?
to the point where we
can't be in the same room?
난 조언은 잘 못하는데
I'm not great at the advice.
비꼬는 말도 괜찮겠어?
Can I interest you
in a sarcastic comment?
치즈 먹을래?
Some cheese?
여보, 왜 브루스 스프링스틴 CD가
캣 스티븐스 케이스에 들어있어?
Honey, why is the Bruce Springsteen CD
in the Cat Stevens case?
스프링스틴 CD를 못 찾겠어서
손에 잡히는 대로 넣었어
If I can't find the right case,
I use the nearest one.
- 캣 스티븐스 CD는 어딨어?
- 제임스 테일러 케이스
-Where is the Cat Stevens CD?
-The James Taylor case.
- 제임스 테일러 CD는?
- 단도직입적으로 말할게
-Where is that CD?
-I'll save you time.
2백 장 중 제대로
들어있는 거 하나도 없어
Two hundred CDs,
not one of them in the right case.
좋아, 발작 일으킬 필요없어
다들 심호흡하고
Okay. No need to panic.
Deep breaths, everyone.
시간을 좀 내서라도
짝을 제대로 찾아 넣어야 돼
We'll just have to put the CDs
in their right cases.
그러러면 어떤 분류 기준이 필요해
알파벳이라든가 장르 같은 거 말야
If we do that, we should
come up with some kind of order.
글쎄, 뭐가 좋을까?
We have to talk this through.
맙소사, 문제가 참 심각하네!
내 가슴이 정말 아파!
Oh, my God, you have such
problems! I feel so terrible for you!
알았어, 미안해
All right. Okay, I'm sorry.
너나 조이나 그 일에만
집중하고 있어서 그래
You're both focusing on
this uncomfortable thing.
대화 주제를 바꿔봐
Change the subject.
다른 얘길 하도록 유도하는 거야
Get him talking about something else.
그래, 그럴듯하네
Yeah, that makes sense.
직장 문제 같은 거 상의해도 되고
Maybe you need his advice
on a work problem..
- 그거 괜찮다
- 좋아
-I could do that.
-Good.
마이애미 바이스 사운드트랙도 들어?
The Miami Vice soundtrack?
Really?
가게에서 그냥 주더라고
They were just giving those away
at the store.
돈 받고 말야
In exchange for money.
안녕
Hey.
난 정말 모르겠어
I really don't know what to tell you.
직장에 관한 일이라면
조이가 도움이 될지도 몰라
Maybe Joey could help you out
with your big work problem.
- 뭐?
- 조이, 있잖아
-What?
-Yeah, Joey, she's..
레이첼이 직장에 큰 문제가 있는데
대책이 떠오르질 않는대
Rachel's got this big work problem.
It is a head-scratcher.
저녁 먹으려면 지금 나가봐야 돼
Know what? If we're gonna make dinner,
we're gonna have to leave.
조이, 레이첼 좀 도와줘
Yeah, Joey, maybe
you could help her out.
- 알았어
- 그리고 참
-Okay.
-Oh, and you know what?
레이첼 도와주는 동안
While you're helping
solve this problem..
손이 심심할 수도 있잖아
그래서 방금 생각해낸 건데
you might want to do something with
your hands. Like, off the top of my head..
저 CD 좀 케이스에 맞게 끼워줘
maybe put the CDs
in their right cases.
어서 가
Here we go.
그래, 직장에 큰 문제가 있다고?
So you have a big work problem?
그래, 그게
Yeah. It's, uh..
그러니까...
Yeah, it's, uh..
있지, 아무것도 아냐
You know, it's nothing.
알았어
Okay.
그럼 난 그만 가볼게
So I think I'm gonna take off.
잠깐, 실은 문제가 있어, 뭐냐면
No, wait, Joey, it is.
It's something. It's..
내 상사 문제야
It's my boss.
- 상사?
- 그래, 그리고
-Yeah?
-Yeah. And, uh..
내 아기도
And my baby.
아기가 뭐?
Yeah?
상사가 아기를 사겠데
My boss wants to buy my baby.
뭐? 맙소사!
What? Oh, my God!
그래, 내가 큰 문제라고 했잖아!
I know, I told you,
it's a really big problem!
- 그 남자가 아기를 사겠데?
- 믿어져?
-He wants to buy your baby?
-Can you believe that?
- 미쳤군
- 나도 그렇게 말했어!
-That's crazy.
-That's what I told him!
- 어떻게 이런 일이 생긴 거야?
- 지금 말해줄게
-How did this even happen?
-Well, I'll tell you.
그러니까 그 사람 부인이
아기를 못 가지거든
See, my boss and his wife,
they can't have children, so..
저번에 크리스마스 파티하는데
And then when we were
at the Christmas party..
술에 취해선 이러더라고
"레이첼, 아길 사고 싶어"
he got drunk and said to me,
"Rachel, I want to buy your baby."
난 네가 상사랑 아기가
관련돼 있다고 하기에
When you said it was a problem
about your boss and the baby..
출산 휴가 문제라고 생각했어
I figured it was
about maternity leave.
그게 있구나
Oh. Yeah.
이 문제보다 훨씬 더 간단하네
Yeah, that would have been
a much simpler problem.
- 안녕하세요
- 당신이군요, 자꾸 만나네요
-Oh, hello.
-Oh, it's you. I see you everywhere.
짐입니다, 짐 넬슨
I'm Jim. Jim Nelson.
안녕, 짐 넬슨
피비예요, 피비 부페이
Hi, Jim-Jim Nelson.
I'm Phoebe-Phoebe Buffay.
- 우연히 자주 만나네요
- 그러게요
-We've seen each other a lot lately.
-Yes.
내일 8시 저녁 먹을 때도
우연히 만나지 않을까요?
Maybe we'll see each other at
dinner tomorrow. Around 8:00?
어쩌면요
Well, maybe we will.
모나?
Mona?
좋아, 내가 연어색 셔츠라면
어디에 있을까?
Okay, if I were a salmon shirt,
where would I be?
강 상류지
Upstream.
젠장, 재밌었는데 아무도 없잖아
Damn, nobody's here
for my good ones.
네 셔츠에 와인 쏟은 거
정말 미안해
I am so sorry I spilled wine
all over your shirt.
- 괜찮아
- 괜찮긴, 아직 축축한걸
-It's okay.
-No, it's still wet.
벗어 봐, 얼룩을 빼야겠어
그 동안 이걸 입고 있어
Let me get it out before it sets.
I have something you could wear.
받아
Here.
여자 셔츠는 입기가 좀 그런데
I don't know if I want to wear
a woman's shirt.
- 아냐, 이거 남자 셔츠야
- 촌스런 꽃분홍이야
-That's a man's shirt.
-Awfully pink.
분홍색 아냐!
It's not pink!
여보, 우린 진짜 잘 만난 것 같아
Honey, we are so meant
to be together.
- 둘 다 애니를 갖고 있잖아
- 둘 다 자기 거야
-We both have the Annie soundtrack.
-Honey, both yours.
조이에 대해 조언해준 거
정말 끝내줬어
Hey, great advice on that Joey thing.
- 그 직장 문제?
- 완벽했다니까
-The work problem?
-lt was perfect.
친구로 되돌아간 것 같아
It felt like he was my friend.
- 무슨 문제라고 했는데?
- 그건 중요하지 않아
-What problem did you say you have?
-Oh, that's not important.
중요한 건 다 잘될 거란 거라고
The point is,
I think everything's gonna be okay.
누구시죠?
May I help you?
내 친구 아기를 돈으로
살 수 있을 것 같아?
You think you can just buy
my friend's baby?
계속 만나다니 신기하지 않아요?
누가 우릴 맺어주려고 하나 봐요
Isn't it funny how we kept meeting?
It's as if someone wants us together.
맞아요, 저예요
Someone does. Me.
참 재치도 넘치셔라
Witty banter. Well done. Good.
- 당신 얘길 해봐요
- 좋아요, 난 안마사예요
-Tell me a little bit about yourself.
-Okay. I'm a masseuse.
- 한때 여기서 일했었죠
- 파티 좋아해요?
-And I used to work at this place..
-Do you like to party?
파티야 좋죠
I like parties.
성격이 화끈하죠?
You're wild, aren't you?
- 네, 조금요
- 나도 그래요
-Yeah, I guess. A little.
-Ain't no thing. I'm wild too.
어쨌든
So anyway..
뉴욕에서 화끈하게
산 지는 오래 됐어요
I've lived in New York,
somewhat wildly, I guess..
14살 때부터죠
for, well, since I was 14.
미안해요, 너무 쳐다봐서
I'm sorry. I'm staring.
이렇게 아름다운 눈은 처음 봐요
It's just that you have
the most beautiful eyes.
- 됐어요
- 그리고 그 가슴!
-Oh, stop it.
-And your breasts!
좋아요
Okay.
조금 세게 나오시네요
Look, you're coming on
a little strong.
첫날이니 눈감아주죠
I'll give you the benefit
of the doubt.
우주도 우릴 축복하는 것 같으니
The universe wants us
to be together.
처음부터 다시 시작하죠
당신 얘길 해봐요
Why don't we start over?
You can tell me about yourself.
- 알았어요
- 좋아요
-All right.
-Okay.
난 포르노 소설을 써요
I write erotic novels..
아동용이오
for children.
- 네?
- 화끈하게 안 팔리죠
-What?
-They're wildly unpopular.
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
그리고 난 박사 학위도 있어요
Also, you might like to know
I have a Ph.D.
- 그래요?
- 네, 포르노 박사라고
-Wow! You do?
-Yep. A pretty huge..
알았어
All right.
- 안녕
- 조이, 어서 와
-Hey.
-Joey, honey, listen.
어젠 정말 고마웠어
내 고민 들어준 거 말야
Thanks for talking to me yesterday.
It meant a lot.
고맙긴, 이젠 걱정 마
Not a problem.
Just so you know..
그 자식이 아기 문제로
더는 귀찮게 안 할 거야
that guy won't be bothering
you about that baby thing anymore.
- 뭐?
- 내가 가서 손봐줬어
-What?
-Let's just say I took care of it.
자세히 말해봐
Let's say more.
걱정 마, 신사답게 얘기했으니까
Don't worry. I told him, very nicely:
'아기는 물건이 아냐! 당장 꺼져!'
"You don't go buying people's babies!
So back off!"
- 뭐?
- 뭐라고?
-What?
난 몰라!
No, no, no!
아기 산다고 한 적 없어!
내가 지어낸 거란 말야!
He doesn't want to buy my baby!
I made that up!
뭐? 왜?
What? Why?
네가 나랑 어색해하니까
얘깃거릴 만들려고!
So we would have something
to talk about!
다른 얘깃거린 없었어?
And you couldn't think
of anything else?
상사가 네 아길
사려고 한다고 그랬어?
You said your boss
wants to buy your baby?
상사를 다그치다니!
난 해고야! 이제 어떡해?
You yelled at my boss!
I'll lose my job! What am I gonna do?
아기를 팔아
You could always sell your baby.
네가 이러다니 믿을 수가 없어!
난 이제 끝장이야!
I can't believe you brought
my boss into it! I'll be fired!
- 네가 거짓말했잖아!
- 모니카가 코치했어!
-You lied to me!
-Well, she told me to!
챈들러가 애니를 2장 갖고 있어!
Chandler has two copies of Annie!
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
- 로스!
- 안녕!
-Ross!
-Hello!
여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
What are you doing?
내 몸 안 만지고 있었으니까
전혀 기분 나빠하지 마
Not touching myself, if that makes
anyone less uncomfortable.
그럼, 전화할게
Okay, then. I'll call you.
안녕하세요, 절 찾으셨다고요?
Morning. You wanted to see me?
어서 들어와, 앉아
Please, come in. Have a seat.
- 저기 사실은...
- 내가 먼저 얘기하지
-Look, Mr. Zelner..
-It's best I speak first.
좋죠
Yeah.
인사과에서 온 리야
내가 증인으로 불렀어
Lee from Human Resources is here
as a witness to our conversation.
맙소사
Oh, God.
내가 어떤 식으로라도 자네 아길
사겠다는 뜻을 비춘 적이 있다면
If I in any way implied
that I wanted to buy your baby..
정말 미안해
I am sorry. Okay?
지난주에 예정일을 물어본 건
Last week, when I asked you
when your due date was..
그냥 궁금해서 그런 거지
아기를 사려고 그런 게 아냐
I certainly did not mean that
I felt that I was "due" your baby.
분명히 알아줬으면 해
I want to be very clear..
난 그 애가 자네 애라는 걸 알아
that I understand
that it's your baby..
돈을 주고 살 의도가 전혀 없어
and it is not mine to purchase.
그 사실만 분명히 해주신다면야
Well, as long as we are clear
about that.
저깄다
There it is.
- 세탁소를 바꾸려고?
- 그래
-Not your regular cleaners.
-I know.
전에 가던 데 가면 그 변태랑
마주칠지도 모르잖아
That creep goes there.
I had to find a new one.
은행도 바꾸고, 포르노 서점도
바꾸고, 슈퍼까지 다 바꿔야 돼
I have to find a new bank,
adult bookstore, grocery store..
- 뭘 바꿔?
- 슈퍼 말야
-What?
-A new grocery store.
우주의 섭리대로라면
멋진 남자였어야 되잖아
The universe said I'd meet a nice guy.
I got that?
언제 우주에 가면 가만 안 둘 거야
When I get up there,
I'm gonna kick some ass.
멋진 남자를 만나게 될 거야
내가 할 수 있다면 너도 가능해
You'll meet someone. If I can meet
a great guy, so can you.
네 말이 맞아, 우린 꼭 만날 거야
Yeah, we both can. And we both will.
- 넌 안 들어와도 돼
- 농담해?
-You didn't have to come in.
-You kidding?
얼룩 없애는 곳이잖아
나한텐 디즈니랜드라고
This is where they get out stains.
This is like Disneyland for me.
저기서 깨끗한 셔츠들
춤추는 거 보고 있을게
I'm gonna be over here watching
the dance of the clean shirts.
실례합니다, 이걸 떨어뜨리신
Excuse me.
I think you dropped..
- 이야!
- 왜요?
-Wow!
-What?
미안해요, 정말 아름다우시군요
Sorry.
You're just so incredibly beautiful.
내가 미안해요
예쁜 걸 어쩌겠어요?
Well, I'm sorry about that too.
But what are you gonna do?
헛소리 같겠지만 운명이 제게
이걸 줍게 한 것 같군요
Don't think I'm crazy,
but I was meant to pick this up.
- 운명을 믿나요?
- 조금요
-Do you believe in that kind of thing?
-A little.
이제야 내 말을 듣네
Now you're talking.
- 커피 마시러 가겠어요?
- 좋아요, 친구한테 얘기하죠
-Want to go for coffee?
-I'd love to. Let me tell my friend.
잉크 자국이네!
얼룩 빼는 거 봐도 돼요?
An ink stain!
Can I watch how you get this out?
혼자 집에 갔나 봐요
She must have left.
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 다 잘됐어
-So? What happened?
-It's all gonna be okay.
내가 고소 안 한다는 데 감격해
유급 출산 휴가를 더 주더라고
They're so happy I'm not suing, I got
an extra month paid maternity leave.
그 돈이 이 아기는 물론
그 어떤 아기에 대한
So long as I understand the money
should not be construed..
계약금도 아니란 걸 알아달래
as a down payment on this
or any other child.
랄프 로렌이 아기 매매와
Ralph Lauren is going
out of their way..
상관없단 걸 증명하려고
애 쓰네
to show they're not
in the baby-buying business.
- 자리 좀 비켜줄래?
- 내 거실에서 나가달라고?
-Give us a minute?
-Kicking me out of my living room?
그래
Yeah.
방으로 갈게
I'll be in there.
거짓말한 거 미안해
난 그냥 어떻게 하면...
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I was just trying to make things..
알아, 다 알아
I know. I know.
효과는 있었어
It kind of worked.
넌 어떤지 몰라도 난 덕분에
우리 일 까맣게 잊고 있었거든
I don't know about you,
but I haven't thought about our thing.
네 말이 맞아
Yeah, you're right.
편한 친구로 되돌아간 것 같아
Yeah. It's kind of been
like "us" again, a little bit.
- 그래, 너무 그리웠어
- 나도
-Yeah, I know. I've missed that.
-Me too.
난 사태가 이렇게 될 줄 몰랐어
I haven't thought about
how I put myself out there..
네가 나랑 맘이 같지 않다니까
and said that stuff.
How you didn't feel the same..
기분이 너무나 어색해지더라고
and how it was really awkward.
내 산과 의사가 날 죽이려 했어
My gynecologist tried to kill me.
물품 번호: J437-A
Item J437-A.
색상: 겨울딸기
Color: winterberry.
안녕, 저기 있잖아
일단 들어와
Hi, listen.
Come here. Come..
어젠 정말 미안했어
I'm so, so sorry about yesterday.
하지만 열쇠를 그렇게 보관하면
내가 어떻게 된다고 했어?
But what did I tell you about leaving
your key outside the door like that?
딴 사람이 아니라
나였던 게 다행인 줄 알아
I mean, you're lucky it was me
and not someone else.
다행이란 말은 뜻이 좀 강하네
I guess lucky is too strong a word.
어쨌든 모나, 정말 미안해
사실은 내가...
Anyway, Mona, I'm really, really sorry.
It's just..
사과는 안 해도 돼
자기가 왜 왔었는지 알아
Listen, you don't have to apologize.
I understand why you were there.
- 알아?
- 그래, 내가 그리워서잖아
-You do?
-Yeah. You still have feelings for me.
솔직히 말해 나도 자기가 그리워
To be honest,
I still have feelings for you.
잘되길 바랬는데 뜻대로 안 됐지
I wish we could work it out,
but we can't.
너무 복잡하더라고
레이첼에다 아기에다 너무
It's too complicated with you
and Rachel and the baby. I just..
인연이 아니었나 봐
It just wasn't meant to be.
네 말이 맞아
Oh, God. You're right.
로스, 우리 강해져야 돼
Ross, we have to be strong.
그럼 나 갈게
Okay, I'm gonna go.
가져도 돼? 널 기억할 수 있게?
Can I? To remember you?
안 돼
No.